LEIGH B. BIENEN PAPERS (APAP312) 1872, 1935, 1951-2011, Undated
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
Leigh B. Bienen Papers1872, 1935, 1951-2011, Undated 1971-2011
nam_apap312
Leigh B. Bienen
23.2
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives, University at Albany, SUNY
The Leigh Bienen Papers include the records of the New Jersey Proportionality Review Project, the Illinois Capital Punishment Reform Study Commission, and the academic research papers of legal scholar Leigh Bienen. The New Jersey records contain material from New Jersey Public Defender Homicide Study directed by Bienen in the mid-1980s. The collection also includes the records from Bienen’s involvement with the New Jersey Proportionality Review Project headed by Special Master David C. Baldus. Also present is material from Leigh Bienen's tenure on the Illinois Capital Punishment Reform Study Commission which resulted in the abolition of the death penalty in that state in 2011. Finally the collection contains Leigh Bienen's scholarly research material during her career teaching at both Princeton University and Northwestern University. Her research focused on proportionality review, the death penalty's monetary costs, and the role of prosecutor discretion.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
All items in the Leigh Bienen Papers were donated by Leigh Bienen in four gifts from 2008 to 2013.
Biographical History
Leigh Bienen graduated from Cornell University in 1960 and undertook graduate work in Economics at M.I.T., and Creative Writing at the University of Iowa before completing her J.D. from Rutgers in 1975. After her admission to the Bar of the Supreme Court of New Jersey in 1975, Bienen wrote on rape law reform in the late 1970s and early 1980s while working briefly as a Research Attorney at the Center of Rape Concern at Philadelphia General Hospital. During this time she also lectured in the Politics Department at Princeton, the University Of Pennsylvania School Of Law, and briefly at the University of California-Berkley School of Law.
Bienen first joined the New Jersey Department of the Public Advocate in 1977 as Assistant Deputy Public Defender and became Director of a Special Projects Section devoted to studying state’s use of capital punishment. Here she directed the New Jersey Public Defender Homicide Study, an empirical study that examined the state’s restoration of the Death Penalty in 1982. The culminating report of the project, The Reimposition of Capital Punishment in New Jersey was cited in State v. Ramseur, the first capital punishment challenge to the New Jersey Supreme Court since 1982. Findings from the study were published in the Rutgers Law Review and the Albany Law Review with Bienen as lead author. Co-authors included Neil Alan Weiner and Deborah W. Denno, other notable death penalty scholars, and Douglas A. Mills, a statistical programming consultant.
The Public Defender Homicide Study influenced the state supreme court which ordered an empirical proportionality review of New Jersey capital cases. Proportionality review is the analysis of an individual death sentence when compared to similar sentences imposed upon similar defendants for similar crimes. Professor David C. Baldus was appointed Special Master to the New Jersey Supreme Court where he developed the methodology for collecting and analyzing data for the project. The state Public Defender contributed data from the Homicide Study and Baldus developed a public collection of data on all relevant homicide cases and headed the New Jersey Proportionality Review Project which included Leigh Bienen. The Project met regularly for three years while they debated the identification of death-eligible cases and all relevant legal and factual issues.
The New Jersey Proportionality Review Project was cited and debated in State v. Marshall II, the first case where the state supreme court conducted proportionality review. The results of the Project suggested race-of-defendant bias, but was criticized due to the overall instability of the data models. Furthermore, the State Attorney General’s Office contended that the "universe" of cases included by the Project was too broad and argued that only similar death sentences--not all death-eligible cases--should be included. Robert O. Marshall became the first of 36 New Jersey capital defendants to have his death sentence upheld by the New Jersey Supreme Court on appeal since 1982. In 1992 the New Jersey State Legislature passed a law that enforced the State Attorney General’s Office’s option that comparison cases in proportionality review would be limited only to cases where a death sentence was imposed. Robert O. Marshall’s death sentence was overturned in 2006 and New Jersey abolished capital punishment in 2007, becoming the first state to do so by legislative act.
Leigh Bienen joined the Woodrow Wilson School of Public and International Affairs as a Lecturer and Administrative Director of the Undergraduate Program in 1991, although she continued to work as a consultant to the New Jersey Department of the Public Advocate for some time. While at Princeton her researched examined proportionality review in state supreme courts and the role of prosecutor discretion in the imposition of the death penalty.
In 1995, Bienen joined the Northwestern University School of Law as a Senior Lecturer. She began researching and writing on the monetary costs of capital punishment, developed the Northwestern University Law School Capital Crimes Database and the Chicago Historical Homicide Project. In 2006 she was appointed a member of the Illinois Capital Punishment Reform Study Committee, a group that was established by Governor George Ryan after his moratorium on executions in 2000 to examine if the death penalty could be carried out fairly. After the committee’s final report in 2011, the state legislature repealed the death penalty that year.
Scope and Content Information
The collection documents Leigh B. Bienen’s scholarly research promoting the abolition of capital punishment in New Jersey and Illinois due to its discriminatory application. Published academic papers, legislative acts, and published judicial decisions used in her research make up much of the collection. Also present are records documenting the New Jersey Public Defender Homicide Study including questionnaires, data reports, and notes. Records from Bienen’s role in the New Jersey Proportionality Review Project are also included. This consists of correspondence, case reports, data gathering information, data tables, drafts, narrative summaries, and multiple case briefs for the major cases involved in the proportionality review including State v. Marshall, State V. Bey, and State v. Martini. Material from the Illinois Capital Punishment Reform Study Committee is also present, consisting of correspondence, meeting minutes, and formal reports. Finally, the collection also includes Leigh Bienen’s teaching materials, notes, and syllabi, as well drafts and final copies of her publications.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into the following series:
Series 1 - New Jersey Proportionality Review Project Records, 1908, 1973-1996, Undated
Series 2 - Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material, 1979-2011, Undated
Series 3 - Illinois Capital Punishment Reform Study Committee Records, 2003-2010
Series 4 - State Death Penalty Law Summaries, 1994-1996, Undated
Series 5 - Reference Materials, 1872, 1935, 1951-2011, Undated
All series are arranged chronologically, with the exception of series 4 which is ordered alphabetically by state.
Subject and Genre Headings
Death Penalty; Criminal Justice and Prisons; Baldus, David C.; Bienen, Leigh B.; Denno, Deborah W.; Weiner, Neal Alan; Discrimination in capital punishment--New Jersey--Statistical methods; Discrimination in capital punishment--United States; Death penalty; Capital punishment--New Jersey; Capital punishment--Illinois; Capital punishment--Law and legislation; Legal research and writing; Legal research--Data processing; Legal research--Illinois; Legal research--New Jersey; Correspondence; Decisions; Legal documents; Legislative acts; Minutes (administrative records); Official reports; Questionnaires; Syllabi
Container List
- New Jersey Proportionality Review Project Records, 1908, 1973-1996, Undated; 1; 6.8
  Arrangement:
  Chronological
  Contents:
  Series contains records from Leigh Bienen's participation in the New Jersey Proportionality Review Project led by Special Master David C. Baldus. This includes correspondence, data gathering information, data tables, and multiple case briefs for the major cases involved in the proportionality review including New Jersey v. Robert O. Marshall, New Jersey v. Marko Bey, and New Jersey v. John Martini.
  - Historical Reports on New Jersey Death Penalty, 1908; 1963; 1969; 1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Legislative History of the Death Penalty, proposed amendments to Senate bill 799, 1973 September 13 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Death Penalty Legislative History, 1979; 1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Public Hearing before the New Jersey Senate Judiciary Committee on Senate bill no. 117 (death penalty), 1982 February 26 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - User Manuel for Prototype Proportionality Review Systems, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - New Jersey v. Thomas C. Ramseur - Brief on Behalf of Defendant - Appellant, Volume 1: Pretrial Motions and Jury Selection, 1984 May 18 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - New Jersey v. Thomas C. Ramseur - Brief on Behalf of Defendant - Appellant, Volume 2: Trial and Sentencing, 1984 May 18 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - New Jersey v. Thomas C. Ramseur - Brief on Behalf of the Attorney General, Amicus Curiae, 1984 September 14 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - New Jersey v. Thomas C. Ramseur - Supplemental Brief and Appendix on Behalf of the Attorney General, Amicus Curiae, 1984 September 14 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - New Jersey v. Thomas C. Ramseur - Appendix of Amicus Curiae, the Attorney General of New Jersey, 1984 September 14 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Binder of Penn Team Memos [1 of 3], 1985 April 1-1987 October 6 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Binder of Penn Team Memos [2 of 3], 1985 April 1-1987 October 6 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Binder of Penn Team Memos [3 of 3], 1985 April 1-1987 October 6 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Homicide Study - Questionnaire and Coding, 1985 May 6; 1985 June 17; Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Codes for Contemporaneous Offense and prior record, 1985 June 17 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Essex County Guidelines for Capital Cases, 1985 July 26 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Essex County and Death Penalty Eligibility, 1985 August 1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Coding Interpretations and Instructions, 1985 November 21 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Coding Interpretations and Instructions, 1985 November 21; Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Michigan Sentences data with notes, ca. 1986 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Robert O. Marshall Death Warrant, 1986 March 05 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Corrected Cases Summaries, 1986 April 7 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Murder Master List, 1986 June 10 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - County Crime Index Treads Percent Change, 1985 January-1986 June; 1986 September (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - ASC Meeting, David Baldas Handout: Prosecutorial Discretion as a source of Arbitrariness and Discrimination, 1986 November 1 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - New Jersey v. George Lazorisak - Trial transcripts, 1987 March 24 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - New Jersey v. George Lazorisak - Trial transcripts, 1987 March 24 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - New Jersey v. George Lazorisak - Trial transcripts, 1987 March 25 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - New Jersey v. George Lazorisak - Trial transcripts, 1987 March 25 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - New Jersey v. George Lazorisak - Trial transcripts, 1987 March 26 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - New Jersey v. George Lazorisak - Trial transcripts, 1987 March 27 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Murder Master List, 1987 May 1; 1989 August 17 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Attorney General and County Prosecutions objections to proportionality review and proportionality seminar, 1987 May 23; 1988 February 24; 1989 April 6 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - McCleskey v. Kemp Amicus Brief from Martin E. Wolfgang, 1987 May 29 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - References list with note from Neil, 1987 June 3 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Penn Team Correspondence, 1988 May 13 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Pennsylvania Data Collection Instrument, 1988 June 14 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - New Jersey v. Alberto Nieves - Brief and Appendix, 1988 June 17 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Essex County Policy and Procedures for Handling AIDs Patients, 1988 July 18 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Pennsylvania first degree murder connections data, 1988 July 21 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Pennsylvania first degree murder connections data, 1988 July 21 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Final Model I - Plea vs. Trial for Death Possible Cases (n=404), 1988 August 19 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Proportionality Review Project, 1988 August 25 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Preliminary Screen Coding Sheet, 1988 November 18 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Instructions for Preliminary Case Screening, 1988 November 19; 1988 December 10 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - New Jersey v. Daniel Martin - Correspondence and notes, 1989; Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Pool Book, 1989 January 3 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Leigh Bienen comments on David C. Baldus New Jersey Proportionality Review Project, 1989 March 7; 1990 May 16 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Review of "The Reimposition of Capital Punishment in New Jersey", 1989 April 4 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Background Information on Project Structure and Preliminary Screen Coding Sheet, 1989 June 12; Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Preliminary Screen Coding Sheet, 1989 June 12 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Background Tables, Keep for Reference, 1989 June 22 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Meeting of July 26,1989 and Data Collection Instrument, 1989 June 23; 1989 June 29 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Progress Report on Preliminary Case Summary, 1989 June 28 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Homicide Master File, 1989 June 29 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Notes, 1989; 1990 April 27 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - New Jersey v. Theodore Wilson, 1989 July 20 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1989 July 26 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1989 July 26 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - New Jersey v. Jose Velez, 1989 August 8 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Stephen P. Klein, et.al., "Relationship of Offender and Victim Race to Death Penalty Sentences in California" with correspondence, 1989 September 8; 1989 November 15; 1989 December 18 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Statement of David C. Baldus before U.S Senate Committee of the January Concerning Arbitrariness and Discrimination in the Imposition of the Death Penalty, 1989 October 2 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Expert Witness Directory, Death Penalty - Migration Phase, 1989 December 4 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - David Baldus and Alternative Universes for Cases for Proportionality Review, 1989 December 6 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - New Jersey Assembly Bill No. 2587, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Opinions of Capital Cases Concerning Proportionality, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Syllabus, New Jersey v. Kef, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - New Jersey Assembly Bills Concerning Cruel and Unusual Punishment and Proportionality Review, 1990; 1991 January 8 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - State Death Penalty Statues - Annotated, 1990 February 9 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - General Accounting Office (GAO) Study on Costs, 1990 March 6 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - New Jersey Procedures for Taking Pleas in Capital Cases, 1990 May 1 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - David C. Baldus, "Interim Report to the New Jersey Supreme Court" (working draft), 1990 May 5 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - David C. Baldus, "New Jersey Proportionality Review Project: Interim Report" (draft), 1990 May 5 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - David C. Baldus, "Interim Report to the New Jersey Supreme Court" [with notes], 1990 May 31 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - International Law and Treaties, 1990 June 25 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Joint Task Force on Death Penalty Litigation in Pennsylvania Report, 1990 July 27 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Florida Death Penalty, 1990 August 10 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - County Prosecutors' Cooperation Statutory Aggravating Factors, 1990 September 14 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Newsweek Article, 1990 September 17 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - New Jersey v. Steven Davis, 1990 September 26 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Envelope - University of New Hampshire, 1990 October 2 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Missouri Proportionality Review Questionnaire, 1990 November 14 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Joseph F. Sullivan, Is Court Killing Death Penalty in New Jersey?, 1990 December 1 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Annotated Summaries of Capital Cases from Other States, 1990 December 28 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Appendix of Additional Thoughts: Problems with the Second Interim Report, ca. 1991 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Detailed Narrative Summaries for Death Eligible Cases [1 of 3], ca. 1991 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Detailed Narrative Summaries for Death Eligible Cases [2 of 3], ca. 1991 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Detailed Narrative Summaries for Death Eligible Cases [3 of 3], ca. 1991 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - New Jersey v. Marshall - Clipping, ca. 1991 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - New Jersey v. Robert O. Marshall - Appendix to Brief Volume IV, ca. 1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Overview of New Jersey Death Penalty Law, ca. 1991 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Public Hearing to Examine the Death Penalty Statue - Transcript, 1991 January 31 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Marshall Pre-Screening File, Atlantic - Essex Counties, 1991 March 9 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Marshall Pre-Screening File, Gloucester - Monmouth Counties, 1991 March 9 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Marshall Pre-Screening File, Morris - Warren Counties, 1991 March 9 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - David Baldus Interim Report to the New Jersey Supreme Court - Appendixes and Tables, 1991 March 13 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - David Baldus Second Interim Report to the New Jersey Supreme Court, 1991 March 13 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence - Proportionality Review, 1991 March 15; 1991 August 12 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - David Baldus, Second Interim Report to the New Jersey Supreme Court, 1991 March 20 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - David Baldus, Second Interim Report to the New Jersey Supreme Court, 1991 March 20 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - New Jersey Death Penalty Defendants, 1991 March 20 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Notes, Thoughts, and Questions on First Interim Report, 1991 April 9; 1991 April 16 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Robert Marshall Clipping, 1991 April 12 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Motion to Postpone Briefing and Argument on Proportionality Review or For Extension of Time to File Brief, 1991 April 12 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Encoded Cases - Douglas Mills, Job number 4919, bin D31 [1 of 3], 1991 April 17 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Encoded Cases - Douglas Mills, Job number 4919, bin D31 [2 of 3], 1991 April 17 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Encoded Cases - Douglas Mills, Job number 4919, bin D31 [3 of 3], 1991 April 17 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Baldus Report Clipping, 1991 April 18 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Handwritten Notes on New Jersey v. Robert O. Marshall Concerning Methodology of Proportionality Review, 1991 April 23 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Memo on Baldus's First and Second Interim Reports on the Proportionality Review Project, from the Penn Team - with handwritten notes, 1991 April 23 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - The Penn Team - Memo on Baldus's First and Second Interim Reports on the Proportionality Review Project, 1991 April 23 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - 20th Wave of Progress Reports - List of Cases with Project Status Clearly in, 1991 May 3 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - 21st Wave of Progress Reports - List of Cases with Project Status Clearly in, 1991 May 3 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Death Penalty Proportionality Review - Minutes, 1991 May 16 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Meeting Minutes - Annotated Copy (no annotations), 1991 May 16 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Preliminary Outline of Proportionality Brief - with handwritten notes, ca. 1991 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Jacob Weisberg, "This Is Your Death", 1991 July 1 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Meeting Minutes and Notes, material from Jack McCarthy, 1991 August 9 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - David C. Baldus, "Death Penalty Proportionality Review Project: Final Report to the New Jersey Supreme Court" (Draft) [1 of 2], 1991 August 10 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - David C. Baldus, "Death Penalty Proportionality Review Project: Final Report to the New Jersey Supreme Court" (Draft) [2 of 2], 1991 August 10 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - David C. Baldus, "Death Penalty Proportionality Review Project: Final Report to the New Jersey Supreme Court" - Appendices and Tables (Draft) [1 of 2], 1991 August 10 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - David C. Baldus, "Death Penalty Proportionality Review Project: Final Report to the New Jersey Supreme Court" - Appendices and Tables (Draft) [2 of 2], 1991 August 10 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - David C. Baldus, "Death Penalty Proportionality Review Project: Final Report to the New Jersey Supreme Court" (Draft), 1991 August 11 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Proportionality Review, 1991 August 13; 1991 October 9 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Progress Report on Preliminary Case Screening, ca. 1991 August 24 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - David Baldus, New Jersey v. Robert O. Marshall: Death Penalty Proportionality Review Project, A Report to The New Jersey Supreme Court (Draft), 1991 August 27 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - David C. Baldus, "Report to the New Jersey Supreme Court concerning State v. Marshall" (Draft), 1991 August 27 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - David C. Baldus, "Report to the New Jersey Supreme Court concerning State v. Marshall" (Draft), 1991 August 27 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Memorandum from David Baldus concerning changes to the final draft of the New Jersey Proportionality Review Project, 1991 August 30 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Technical Appendix 10: Logistic Multiple - Regression Models and Scales, 1991 September 5 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - David Baldus, Death Penalty Proportionality Review, 1991 September 6 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Corrections to database DCI, Questions for September Meeting, 1991 September 6 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - New Jersey Court Sentencing decisions, ca. 1991 September 19 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - David C. Baldus, "Death Penalty Proportionality Review Project Final Report to the New Jersey Supreme Court, 1991 September 24 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - David C. Baldus, Death Penalty Proportionality Review Project - Final Report to the New Jersey Supreme Court, 1991 September 24 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - David C. Baldus, Death Penalty Proportionality Review Project - Final Report to the New Jersey Supreme Court - Appendices and Tables [1 of 2], 1991 September 24 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - David C. Baldus, Death Penalty Proportionality Review Project - Final Report to the New Jersey Supreme Court - Appendices and Tables [2 of 2], 1991 September 24 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - David C. Baldus, Report to the New Jersey Supreme Court concerning New Jersey v. Robert O. Marshall, 1991 September 24 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - David C. Baldus, "Report to the New Jersey Supreme Court concerning New Jersey v. Marshall", 1991 September 24 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - David C. Baldus, "Report to the New Jersey Supreme Court concerning State v. Marshall" (Copy for public dissemination), 1991 September 24 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Changes to Narrative Summaries, 1991 September 24 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Changes to Narrative Summaries, 1991 September 24 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - New Jersey's Capital Sentencing System: the Statutory Aggravating and Mitigating Circumstances, 1991 September 24 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Statement of Director Robert T. Winter on David C. Baldus Report, 1991 September 25 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Mail-It: Death or CA w13 Proportionality Review and date after 1986, 1991 September 26 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Mail-It: Death or CA w13 Proportionality Review and date after 1989, 1991 September 26 (Box 4, Folder 28)